Guide to the Administrative Papers of President John Crittenden Sawhill 1974-1981 (Bulk 1975-1979) RG.3.0.8
New York University Archives
- Series XI: Student Affairs
  - Student Center; LOEB, Sep 1975-Aug 1976 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Student Conduct, May 1976 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Addendum I: MSS: "Energy: Managing the Transition," Trilateral Commission
  Documentation of the preparation of this study/report fills the final portion of Box 78, one complete box (Box 79), and the first section of a third box, (Box 80), for a total of 1.75 linear feet. Box 78, folders 18-19, contain material related to some of the design and distribution considerations associated with John Crittenden Sawhill's role as primary author of this study undertaken for the Trilateral Commission. Box 79, folders 1-4 contains further associated materials, while folders 5-9 and, in Box 80, folders 1-6, contain evolving drafts of the document which became the final version of the publication, 'ENERGY: MANAGING THE TRANSITION,' Sawhill, John C., Oshima, Keichi, Maull, Hanns W, Trilateral Commission Task Force Report: 17, 1978. Where there were hand-edited and clean versions of given dated drafts, hand-edited versions only were retained. Bound unedited manuscripts marked DISCUSSION DRAFT were discarded.
  - Acknowledgements for MSS Distribution, Aug 1978-Jun 1979 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Art Work, undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Press Coverage, Nov 1978-Jul 1979 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Programmatic Materials and Matters, Jul 1977-Jul 1979 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Study on International Energy Issues, May 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Trialogue No. 18; Energy, Industrial Relations, and Trilateral Economic Problems, Jun 1978 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Working Copy (Bound Discussion Draft), Aug 1977 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Working Copy, Sep 1977 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Working Copies, Dec 1977 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Working Copies, Jan 1978 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Working Copies, Feb 1978 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Working Copies (1), Mar 1978 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Working Copies (2), Mar 1978 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Working Copy, Apr 1978 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Working Copy, May 1978 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Working Version, Jun 1978 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Working Version (Bound Discussion Draft), Jun 1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Addendum II: Restricted Materials (not available until 2016)
  Conditions Governing Access
  These contents of Box 80, folders 7-14, .5 linear feet, will be available in 2016.
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Restricted, undated (Box 80, Folder 14)